Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office. Media Center Audiovisual Collection, 1953-2015 and undated RL.00734
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Optical Media (CDs, DVDs), 1993-2015; undated; 4
  - JWTwo--Diamond Trading Company Christmas case study, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0149)
  - JWTwo--Diamond Trading Company Dandelions, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0150)
  - JWTwo--Diamond Trading Company Hands edit :30, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0151)
  - JWTwo--Diamond Trading Company Journey, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0152)
  - JWTwo--Diamond Trading Company Journey revised, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0153)
  - JWTwo--Diamond Trading Company London montage video for Unilever presentation, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0154)
  - JWTwo--Diamond Trading Company spots, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0155)
  - JWTwo--Diamond Trading Company Speechless in Times Square, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0156)
  - JWTwo--Digital Day Andrew Keen, Undated (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0157)
  - JWTwo--Digital Day David Clark, Undated (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0158)
  - JWTwo--Digital Day David Moore, Undated (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0159)
  - JWTwo--Digital Day Jamie Goldblatt, Undated (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0160)
  - JWTwo--Digital Day Jonathan Bulkeley, Undated (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0161)
  - JWTwo--Digital Day Ricky Van Veen, Undated (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0162)
  - JWTwo--Domino's Anything Goes, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0163)
  - JWTwo--Domino's Anything Goes 3:45, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0164)
  - JWTwo--Domino's Anything Goes case study, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0165)
  - JWTwo--Domino's Anything Goes Titanium video, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0166)
  - JWTwo--Domino's case study, Undated (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0167)
  - JWTwo--Domino's spots, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0168)
  - JWTwo--Domino's spots for Bob Jeffrey, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0169)
  - JWTwo--Domino's YouTube/eBay, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0170)
  - JWTwo--Droppelmina and Wupperstrand, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0171)
  - JWTwo--DVD 2: Times of India, Key to Reserva, Ford Fabrica, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0172)
  - JWTwo--HSBC radio, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0173)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Bailey's, Stouffer's, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0174)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Cadbury, Diageo Smirnoff, Domino's, Jenny Craig, Johnson & Johnson, Kimberly Clark, HSBC, Neosporin, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0175)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Cadbury, Kimberly Clark, Macy's, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0176)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Cadbury, Smirnoff, Jenny Craig, Johnson & Johnson, Unilever, Domino's, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0177)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Diageo Smirnoff, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0178)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Diageo Smirnoff, Diamond Trading, Jenny Craig, Schick, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0179)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Diageo Smirnoff, Domino's, Jenny Craig, Unilever Sunsilk, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0180)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Diageo Smirnoff, Diamond Trading, Jenny Craig, Schick, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0181)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Diamond Trading (DTC), 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0182)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Diamonds for Futures, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0183)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: HSBC, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0184)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Huggies, Ablify, Zyrtec, Cannes Bike, HSBC, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0185)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Huggies, Sudafed, Zyrtec, NY Cared, Stride, Listerine, Rolaids, Jenny Craig, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0186)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: JetBlue, Johnson & Johnson, Kleenex, Listerine, Macy's, Smirnoff, Scott Tissue, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0187)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: JetBlue, Smirnoff, Madmen animation, Listerine, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0188)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Scott Tissue, Benadryl, Visine, Rolaids, HSBC, Smirnoff, Macy's, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0189)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Kleenex, Scott Tissue, Rolaids, Listerine, Smirnoff, Macy's, JetBlue, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0190)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Macy's, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0191)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Macy's, Domino's, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0192)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Trident, Smirnoff, Huggies, Band Aid, Reach, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0193)
  - JWTwo--ECD Meeting: Welch's, Jenny Craig, Boostup.org, Domino's, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0194)
  - JWTwo--ECD Q4 Challenge: Swedish Fish, Cuervo, MTV, Royal Caribbean, Abilify, Microsoft, Sudafed, HSBC, Stouffers, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0195)
  - JWTwo--Eric Steinhauser, 2004 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0196)
  - JWTwo--Ford Bold Moves, 2009 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0197)
  - JWTwo--Ford Bold Moves 9:36, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0198)
  - JWTwo--Ford Bold Moves 13:41, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0199)
  - JWTwo--Ford Bold Moves, Undated (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0200)
  - JWTwo--Ford Bold Moves Case Study, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0201)
  - JWTwo--Ford Brand Manifesto, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0202)
  - JWTwo--Ford Division Broadcast Creative: F-150, GT, Mustang, 2005 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0203)
  - JWTwo--Ford Drive One, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0204)
  - JWTwo--Ford Everybody In, 2010 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0205)
  - JWTwo--Ford International Television Spots, 2005 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0206)
  - JWTwo--Fox Business News, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0207)
  - JWTwo--Fox News, Cavuto, Bob Jeffrey segment, 2005 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0208)
  - JWTwo--Freixenet, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0209)
  - JWTwo--Freixenet Key to Reserva, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0210)
  - JWTwo--Future of Men book release, 2005 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0211)
  - JWTwo--Goalie rev logo, 2005 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0212)
  - JWTwo--Goldsmith/Jeffrey "Graves", 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0213)
  - JWTwo--Good Morning America, Super Bowl segment, 2006 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0214)
  - JWTwo--Good Morning America, Welch's segment, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0215)
  - JWTwo--Gifting Moments, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0216)
  - JWTwo--Halls 2004-2007, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0217)
  - JWTwo--Halls College Film, 2010 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0218)
  - JWTwo--Halls Defense radio, 2010 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0219)
  - JWTwo--Halls Kelly Awards, Undated (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0220)
  - JWTwo--Halls spots, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0221)
  - JWTwo--Halls radio Announcer Throwdown, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0222)
  - JWTwo--HBS presentation, 2004 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0223)
  - JWTwo--History of Attention 4:01, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0224)
  - JWTwo--HSBC, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0225)
  - JWTwo--HSBC, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0226)
  - JWTwo--HSBC brand video, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0227)
  - JWTwo--HSBC Lumberjack US 1:40, 2009 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0228)
  - JWTwo--HSBC Paparazzi/Parasites, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0229)
  - JWTwo--HSBC Piggy case study for GCC 2:59, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0230)
  - JWTwo--HSBC Premier "The Search" Quicktime, Undated (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0231)
  - JWTwo--HSBC Titanium new, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0232)
  - JWTwo--HSBC Titanium video, Nick Scotting, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0233)
  - JWTwo--Huffington Post discussion panel webcast, Cannes, 2006 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0234)
  - JWTwo--Huggies, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0235)
  - JWTwo--Huggies, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0236)
  - JWTwo--Huggies Twist and Turn animatic for testing only, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0237)
  - JWTwo--Huggies and Pull-Ups Cannes on-air, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0238)
  - JWTwo--Ice animatic, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0239)
  - JWTwo--Ilori animated film, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0240)
  - JWTwo--Ilori brand kit, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0241)
  - JWTwo--Ilori H264 QT for displays, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0242)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue 16 spots, 2006 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0243)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue Booth video, 2006 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0244)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue case study for New Balance RFP, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0245)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue CEO's Welcome Aboard, Undated (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0246)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue creative Powerpoint for Stuart Elliott, 2006 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0247)
  - JWTwo--JetBlueDunkin' Donuts, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0248)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue Happy Jetting case study, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0249)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue Jetting Is agency version, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0250)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue President's Message; Welcome Aboard, Undated (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0251)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue Happy Jetting; Rolex Ashes and Snow, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0252)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue Story, 2006 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0253)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue Story, 2006 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0254)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue Storybooth, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0255)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue Storybooth 4:28, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0256)
  - JWTwo--JetBlue Storybooth; Brian Burik iPod; Steins; Extra Leg Room, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0257)
  - JWTwo--Jonathan Harris, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0258)
  - JWTwo--Johnson & Johnson competitive reel, 2009 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0259)
  - JWTwo--Johnson & Johnson: US Zyrtec, UK Immodium; US Listerine; Australia Listerine; Canada Tylenol, 2009 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0260)
  - JWTwo--Jose Cuervo Podcasts, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0261)
  - JWTwo--Jose Cuervo Podcasts, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0262)
  - JWTwo--JWT 1980s reel, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0263)
  - JWTwo--JWT 2008 Olympic work (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0264)
  - JWTwo--JWT 2009 overview (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0265)
  - JWTwo--JWT Adweek Report Card, 2009 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0266)
  - JWTwo--JWT Creative Highlights, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0267)
  - JWTwo--JWT Creative Highlights, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0268)
  - JWTwo--JWT Creative Highlights, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0269)
  - JWTwo--JWT Creative Highlights, Undated (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0270)
  - JWTwo--JWT Creative Innovation reel, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0271)
  - JWTwo--JWT Creative reel, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0272)
  - JWTwo--JWT Creative reel: Wilkinson, Kimberly Clark, Kit Kat, Times of India, Freixenet, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0273)
  - JWTwo--JWT Creative reel: Wilkinson; Smirnoff; Thrifty; Kleenex; Ford Ka; Shell; Kit Kat; Times of India; DTC; Freixenet, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0274)
  - JWTwo--JWT Global Creative Challenge, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0275)
  - JWTwo--JWT Global reel: Red Cross; Heineken; Macy's; Kotex; Kit Kat; JetBlue; VicRoads; MyFirstBook, 2010 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0276)
  - JWTwo--Johnson & Johnson global reel, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0277)
  - JWTwo--JWT Headquarters New York, 2009 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0278)
  - JWTwo--JWT Historical Reel, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0279)
  - JWTwo--JWT History data dvd, 2011 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0280)
  - JWTwo--JWT History 45:00, 2011 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0281)
  - JWTwo--JWT New York Non-traditional storytelling 46:11, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0282)
  - JWTwo--Kill the Word, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0283)
  - JWTwo--Kimberly Clark Check-In, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0284)
  - JWTwo--Kimberly Clark Cottonelle, Andrex, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0285)
  - JWTwo--Kimberly Clark current creative, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0286)
  - JWTwo--Kimberly Clark current creative, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0287)
  - JWTwo--Kleenex Behind the Scenes, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0288)
  - JWTwo--Kleenex Kelly Awards, Undated (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0289)
  - JWTwo--Kleenex Let It Out US Aired, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0290)
  - JWTwo--Kleenex Let It Out behind the scenes, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0291)
  - JWTwo--Kleenex Let It Out TV and Web, Undated (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0292)
  - JWTwo--Kleenex Let It Out, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0293)
  - JWTwo--Kleenex Let It Out TV, 2008 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0294)
  - JWTwo--Kleenex press reel for Gordon Knapp, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0295)
  - JWTwo--Kleenex press reel for Gordon Knapp, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0296)
  - JWTwo--Kleenex radio for Oprah, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0297)
  - JWTwo--Kleenex Webisodes reel, 2007 (Box O4, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0298)
  - JWTwo--Landscapers; Tollbooth; Big Bag, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0299)
  - JWTwo--Lead India, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0300)
  - JWTwo--Letitout.com, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0301)
  - JWTwo--LL Bean agency version, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0302)
  - JWTwo--LL Bean; DC Shoes; Diageo; JetBlue, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0303)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites 1 :90 trailer, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0304)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites 1 nooner episodes (9 total), 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0305)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites 1 TBS episodes (65 total), 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0306)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites 2 case study, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0307)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites 2 case study V2, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0308)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites 2 case study video 3:00, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0309)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites EPK P2 cam, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0310)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites EPK tape 2-3, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0311)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites EPK tape 4-5, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0312)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites EPK tape 6, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0313)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites EPK tape 7, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0314)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites intro film; titanium case study; season 2 case study; Ford Bold Moves case study; JetBlue CEO viral Ch. 1-3; Nokie Bruce Lee Ping Pong viral; Key to Reserva, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0315)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites "I Finally Talked to God"; "Don't Check Your Email"; "Cannot Return", 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0316)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites Intro film, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0317)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites Intro film longer version, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0318)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites; Hairapy Guys; Gethairapy.com, 2006 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0319)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites longer version with revised ending episodes, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0320)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites Paul Reiser broadcast press soundbites, 2006 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0321)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites Paul Reiser media tour, 2006 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0322)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites season two TBS and Internet episodes, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0323)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites Too Hot episodes, 2006 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0324)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites unit photography, 2006 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0325)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites 1 WalMart episodes (3 total), 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0326)
  - JWTwo--Lovebites WWC rev, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0327)
  - JWTwo--Lux Catherine Zeta Jones, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0328)
  - JWTwo--Lux Films, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0329)
  - JWTwo--Macy's 1986, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0330)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Believe 09 English and Spanish, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0331)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Brand Experience, 2011 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0332)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Brand Fall 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0333)
  - JWTwo--Macy's case study brand TV, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0334)
  - JWTwo--Macy's case study brand TV, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0335)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Makeover; 150 year anthem, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0336)
  - JWTwo--Macy's media reel, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0337)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Morning; Martha, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0338)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Morning; Martha; Evening, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0339)
  - JWTwo--Macy's New Guy; Carla; Access Hollywood; E! News, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0340)
  - JWTwo--Macy's TV spots, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0341)
  - JWTwo--Macy's World Retail Congress; Marketing Campaign of the Year Award Entry 2008, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0342)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Yes Virginia animation, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0343)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Yes Virginia film clip Film Lions data CD, 2010 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0344)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Yes Virginia entry data DVD, 2010 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0345)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Yes Virginia data DVD, 2010 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0346)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Yes Virginia film trailer data CD, 2010 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0347)
  - JWTwo--Macy's Yes Virginia, There Is a Santa Claus, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0348)
  - JWTwo--Madmen disc 1 episode 1 clip 2 chaos video: Times of India; Nike Cricket; Levi's Slim; Greet Tea Partay; Huggies Geyser; Benilyn; Schick; Ford, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0349)
  - JWTwo--Marian Salzman TV appearances, CNBC Morning Call; Fox and Friends, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0350)
  - JWTwo--Marian Salzman Ubersexual segment; Today Show, 2006 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0351)
  - JWTwo--Master reel for Johnson and Johnson, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0352)
  - JWTwo--Mavericks at Work book launch, 2006 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0353)
  - JWTwo--Microsoft Bing spots, 2010 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0354)
  - JWTwo--Microsoft It's Everybody's Business, Undated (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0355)
  - JWTwo--Microsoft Manifesto Combined; Real Voices, Kevin Martin, Martine Reardon, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0356)
  - JWTwo--Microsoft pitch video, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0357)
  - JWTwo--Microsoft pitch video, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0358)
  - JWTwo--MTV Choose or Lose, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0359)
  - JWTwo--My Neurotransmitters history; Zelnorm; Advair, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0360)
  - JWTwo--Nat Whitten, 2004 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0361)
  - JWTwo--NBC Today Show; Where in the World is Matt Lauer featuring Tom Doctoroff, Greater China CEO, 2005 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0362)
  - JWTwo--Nestle; JetBlue; Stride, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0363)
  - JWTwo--Nestle Skinny Cow, 2011 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0364)
  - JWTwo--Next Big Idea, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0365)
  - JWTwo--Nike commercials; Can Can't Air Jordan; Role Model Charles Barkley, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0366)
  - JWTwo--Pepsi Chase, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0367)
  - JWTwo--Pepsi final show reel Faith Popcorn, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0368)
  - JWTwo--Phonestar case study, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0369)
  - JWTwo--Polternder Stahldrache Eine Faszinierende Reise Durch Die Geschichte Der Wuppertaler Schwebebahn, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0370)
  - JWTwo--Pristiq Talking About Menopause, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0371)
  - JWTwo--Pristiq audio boards, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0372)
  - JWTwo--Q4 ECD Meeting disc 1, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0373)
  - JWTwo--Q4 ECD Meeting disc 2; HSBC Magazine Takeover; Diageo Jose Cuervo Q4 case study, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0374)
  - JWTwo--Recent Benedryl creative, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0375)
  - JWTwo--Rock the Vote; Domino's; JetBlue, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0376)
  - JWTwo--Rolex anthem Michael Caine, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0377)
  - JWTwo--Rolex anthem POV, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0378)
  - JWTwo--Rolex Ashes and Snow, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0379)
  - JWTwo--Royal Caribbean case study, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0380)
  - JWTwo--Royal Caribbean Postcards Caribbean shoot, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0381)
  - JWTwo--Sean Boyle, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0382)
  - JWTwo--Sir Martin Sorrell Paley Center Tribute without Rupert Murdoch, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0383)
  - JWTwo--Sir Martin Sorrell Paley Center Tribute X-rated version, 2009 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0384)
  - JWTwo--Smirnoff audioboards, 2010 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0385)
  - JWTwo--Smirnoff Green Tea Partay, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0386)
  - JWTwo--Smirnoff Green Tea Partay, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0387)
  - JWTwo--Smirnoff Green Tea Partay, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0388)
  - JWTwo--Smirnoff spots, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0389)
  - JWTwo--Smirnoff North, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0390)
  - JWTwo--Smirnoff Signature, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0391)
  - JWTwo--Smirnoff; Sunsilk, 2007 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0392)
  - JWTwo--Smirnoff Tea Partay on iCaught (ABC), 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0393)
  - JWTwo--Sorrell clip CNBC, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0394)
  - JWTwo--Sour Patch Kids, 2008 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0395)
  - JWTwo--Steve Le Neveu, 2005 (Box O5, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0396)
  - JWTwo--Stride spots, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0397)
  - JWTwo--Stride integrated case study, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0398)
  - JWTwo--Stride Monochewcliosis, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0399)
  - JWTwo--Stride Photobooth V1, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0400)
  - JWTwo--Stride Photobooth, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0401)
  - JWTwo--Stride Photobooth award video, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0402)
  - JWTwo--Stride Photobooth award video, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0403)
  - JWTwo--Stride Photo Booth case version 1, Undated (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0404)
  - JWTwo--Stride Spit It Out integrated case 4:49, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0405)
  - JWTwo--Stride Staring Contest, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0406)
  - JWTwo--Stride Tick Tock Digital Board, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0407)
  - JWTwo--Stride TV, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0408)
  - JWTwo--Sundance Billy Collins titanium, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0409)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Awards, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0410)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Color Showdown, 2008 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0411)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Color Showdown.com, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0412)
  - JWTwo--Sunsilk Color Showdown.com, 2007 (Box O6, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0413)